geninfo.com 2015-06-10

# GIS | General Information Services | Privacy

Protecting privacy has always been a top priority at GIS. We believe that a strong privacy policy is good business. To underscore our commitment to privacy, we have amended our online privacy policy on our websites.

The policy includes our corporate privacy principles and Fair Information Practice Principles of notice, choice, access, security, and accountability.

This online privacy policy applies to all sites listed above. They are owned and operated by General Information Services, Inc. (GIS), 917 Chapin Dr., Chapin, SC 29036, (888) 333-5696.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

I. Personally-identifiable information

These sites only collect personally-identifiable information from you if you choose to provide this information and to process a transaction that you requested. Personally-identifiable information collected with your consent may include, for example, name, e-mail address, resume information, or any inquires you may make through our websites. GIS only provides personally-identifiable information to third-parties in its normal course of business for two reasons: (1) in order to complete a transaction you requested, such as running a credit report through TransUnion, and (2) as required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.

II. Cookies

"Cookies" are messages that web servers (computers that deliver web pages) exchange with web browsers (programs that support website interaction, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer). GIS uses these messages in our customer web applications to simplify and enhance the user experience. GIS does not store any personally-identifiable information in cookies. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems, nor can they be used to spread viruses or access your computer's hard drive.

III. Non-personally-identifiable information

This site also collects non-personally-identifiable information. For example, as you browse our websites, we may collect information about your visit, but not about you personally. Via web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit our sites (e.g., Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, etc.).

### INFORMATION USE AND CONSUMER CHOICE

The information collected by our websites are used only for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request, maintaining your account (if you have one), and for the administration, review and/or the improvement the content of our websites.

We may contact you in response to your comments or inquiries, as part of the maintenance of your account with us (if you have one), or in order to complete a transaction that you requested.

If you decide that you do not want to receive further e-mails regarding your inquiry from GIS, you can reply to the e-mail or use the telephone number (888) 333-5696 with a request that we not continue to e-mail you. We do not use outside data sources to enrich marketing data obtained online.

### ACCESS AND CORRECTION

As an information company, we value having our data as accurate as possible. Accordingly, we strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through our websites. We believe the individual is invaluable in ensuring that their data is complete and accurate. We will provide you access to your personally-identifiable information for as long as we maintain that information in an accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our websites. If you wish to correct any inaccurate information you have submitted to any of these sites, please call (888)333-5696.

### SECURITY

We take steps to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally-identifiable information collected through this website. We recognize the importance of security for all personally-identifiable information collected by our website. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers.

Once we receive personally-identifiable information, we take steps to protect its security on our systems. In the event we request or transmit sensitive information, such as Social Security Numbers, we use accepted industry standards, such as 128-bit secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption.

We strictly limit access to personally-identifiable information to those employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities.

### POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right the revise this policy as needed. As such, in the event revisions are made, we will prominently post announcements on our websites that describe the details of the revisions.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION DISCLOSURE: UNITED STATES OR OVERSEAS

In preparing a consumer report or investigative consumer report, we only send information about the subject of the report outside the United States if our client asks for information from a jurisdiction outside the United States. For example, if a prospective employee worked outside of the United States, our client might ask for a criminal history report for the country in which the prospective employee worked. When we do this kind of report, we send enough information to identify the subject of the report.

### FOR MORE INFORMATION

For more information about our privacy practices or policies, please contact our Disputes Department at P.O. Box 353, Chapin, South Carolina 29036, or by telephone at (866) 265-4917, or by email to info@geninfo.com.

Protecting privacy has always been a top priority at GIS. We believe that a strong privacy policy is good business. To underscore our commitment to privacy, we have amended our online privacy policy on our websites.

The policy includes our corporate privacy principles and Fair Information Practice Principles of notice, choice, access, security, and accountability.

This online privacy policy applies to all sites listed above. They are owned and operated by General Information Services, Inc. (GIS), 917 Chapin Dr., Chapin, SC 29036, (888) 333-5696.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

I. Personally-identifiable information

These sites only collect personally-identifiable information from you if you choose to provide this information and to process a transaction that you requested. Personally-identifiable information collected with your consent may include, for example, name, e-mail address, resume information, or any inquires you may make through our websites. GIS only provides personally-identifiable information to third-parties in its normal course of business for two reasons: (1) in order to complete a transaction you requested, such as running a credit report through TransUnion, and (2) as required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.

II. Cookies

"Cookies" are messages that web servers (computers that deliver web pages) exchange with web browsers (programs that support website interaction, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer). GIS uses these messages in our customer web applications to simplify and enhance the user experience. GIS does not store any personally-identifiable information in cookies. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems, nor can they be used to spread viruses or access your computer's hard drive.

III. Non-personally-identifiable information

This site also collects non-personally-identifiable information. For example, as you browse our websites, we may collect information about your visit, but not about you personally. Via web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit our sites (e.g., Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, etc.).

### INFORMATION USE AND CONSUMER CHOICE

The information collected by our websites are used only for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request, maintaining your account (if you have one), and for the administration, review and/or the improvement the content of our websites.

We may contact you in response to your comments or inquiries, as part of the maintenance of your account with us (if you have one), or in order to complete a transaction that you requested.

If you decide that you do not want to receive further e-mails regarding your inquiry from GIS, you can reply to the e-mail or use the telephone number (888) 333-5696 with a request that we not continue to e-mail you. We do not use outside data sources to enrich marketing data obtained online.

### ACCESS AND CORRECTION

As an information company, we value having our data as accurate as possible. Accordingly, we strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through our websites. We believe the individual is invaluable in ensuring that their data is complete and accurate. We will provide you access to your personally-identifiable information for as long as we maintain that information in an accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our websites. If you wish to correct any inaccurate information you have submitted to any of these sites, please call (888)333-5696.

### SECURITY

We take steps to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally-identifiable information collected through this website. We recognize the importance of security for all personally-identifiable information collected by our website. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers.

Once we receive personally-identifiable information, we take steps to protect its security on our systems. In the event we request or transmit sensitive information, such as Social Security Numbers, we use accepted industry standards, such as 128-bit secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption.

We strictly limit access to personally-identifiable information to those employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities.

### POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right the revise this policy as needed. As such, in the event revisions are made, we will prominently post announcements on our websites that describe the details of the revisions.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION DISCLOSURE: UNITED STATES OR OVERSEAS

In preparing a consumer report or investigative consumer report, we only send information about the subject of the report outside the United States if our client asks for information from a jurisdiction outside the United States. For example, if a prospective employee worked outside of the United States, our client might ask for a criminal history report for the country in which the prospective employee worked. When we do this kind of report, we send enough information to identify the subject of the report.

### FOR MORE INFORMATION

For more information about our privacy practices or policies, please contact our Disputes Department at P.O. Box 353, Chapin, South Carolina 29036, or by telephone at (866) 265-4917, or by email to info@geninfo.com.

## Contact GIS

  * General Inquiries
  * Questions

  * Request a Copy
  * Dispute a Background Check

GIS provides background screening services to many organizations. GIS does not make hiring decisions for our clients and is unable to comment on any of their hiring processes. Please note that if an employer notified you of any adverse findings in a background report GIS provided to them, you may have already received a copy of your report, a Summary of Your Rights under the Fair Credit Reporting Act and had the opportunity to dispute the accuracy or completeness of any information contained in the report with GIS before the adverse action was taken. You also have the right to obtain an additional free copy of the report within 60 days of your receipt of that letter by contacting General Information Services at the address or phone number below or by filling out the contact form on the next page to obtain a free copy.

_**NOTE: Please DO NOT provide personally identifiable information in our contact forms (such as a social security number or date of birth). Only provide what is requested in the form.**_

#### GIS Consumer Relations & Disputes Contact Information:

General Information Services (GIS)

PO Box 353

Chapin, SC 29036

Toll-free Phone: 1-866-265-4917

Toll-free Fax: 1-866-265-4921

×

## Contact GIS' Disputes Department

GIS provides background screening services to many organizations. GIS does not make hiring decisions for our clients and is unable to comment on any of their hiring processes. Please note that if an employer notified you of any adverse findings in a background report GIS provided to them, you may have already received a copy of your report, a Summary of Your Rights under the Fair Credit Reporting Act and had the opportunity to dispute the accuracy or completeness of any information contained in the report with GIS before the adverse action was taken. You also have the right to obtain an additional free copy of the report within 60 days of your receipt of that letter by contacting General Information Services at the address or phone number below or by filling out the contact form below to obtain a free copy.

_**NOTE: Please DO NOT provide personally identifiable information in our contact forms (such as a social security number or date of birth). Only provide what is requested in the form.**_

#### GIS Consumer Relations & Disputes Contact Information:

General Information Services (GIS)

PO Box 353

Chapin, SC 29036

Toll-free Phone: 1-866-265-4917

Toll-free Fax: 1-866-265-4921

×

## Request a FREE copy of your Background Check.

GIS provides background screening services to many organizations. GIS does not make hiring decisions for our clients and is unable to comment on any of their hiring processes. Please note that if an employer notified you of any adverse findings in a background report GIS provided to them, you may have already received a copy of your report, a Summary of Your Rights under the Fair Credit Reporting Act and had the opportunity to dispute the accuracy or completeness of any information contained in the report with GIS before the adverse action was taken. You also have the right to obtain an additional free copy of the report within 60 days of your receipt of that letter by contacting General Information Services at the address or phone number below or by filling out the contact form below to obtain a free copy.

_**NOTE: Please DO NOT provide personally identifiable information in our contact forms (such as a social security number or date of birth). Only provide what is requested in the form.**_

#### GIS Consumer Relations & Disputes Contact Information:

General Information Services (GIS)

PO Box 353

Chapin, SC 29036

Toll-free Phone: 1-866-265-4917

Toll-free Fax: 1-866-265-4921

×
